

## Phattanothai Pukham

# Software Developer

## **Personal Information**

Nick Name	Fluke
Military Status	Reservist
Date of Availaility	Immediately

I don't have much work experience. But I am ready to learn and develop. I'm the type of person who likes a challenge. easy to get along with I like to try new things and develop myself all the time.

I hope that we will have the opportunity to work together.

#### **Contect**

0635957755
phattanothai.pukham@gmail.com
96 Moo.6 Tambon
Thanthong, Amphur Phan,
Chiang Rai 57250
https://github.com/phattanotai
https://phattanothai-pukham-
web.netlify.app

#### Skills

Graphic	Design
Fair	
UX/UI I	Design
Fair	
Coding	
	Fluent
Databa	Se Se
	Good
Server	
	Standard
Researc	ch
	Excellent

### **EDUCATION**

2012-2016 Bachelor of Science Program in Computer Science

Suan Sunandha Rajabhat University

GPA 3.21

2009-2016 Pali language

Wat Paknam Bhasicharoen

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

1 Aug. 2022 - Present Frontend Developer at Driven Digital Co.,Ltd.

(Web App)

Jan. 2022 - Present Freelance Software Developer (Web App,

Mobile App, REST API)

1 Nov. 2020 - Jan. 2022 Full Stack Developer Full-Time (Web App,

Mobile App, REST API) at OTEN

INNOVATION, (Remote Work)

1 Jun. 2019 - 31 Oct. 2020 Programmer Full-Time (Web App, Mobile App,

tcp server, REST API) at World Gps Tracker

Co.,Ltd, Chiang Rai http://wgtgps.net

1 May 2017 – 30 Apr. 2019 Fort Mengraimaharaj Hospital, Chiang Rai

#### **ABILITIES**

Coding Nodejs, Javascript, Typescript, PHP, SQL, Python

Flask, Expressjs, Slim, Nestjs

Angular, Vuejs, React, Nextjs, Ionic, Nuxtjs, React Native, Bootstrap, Material Design, Tailwind CSS, Ant Design One Signal, Pusher, Selenium, Graphql, Apollo, Threejs

Sequelize, TypeORM, Mongoose Google Map, Leaflet Map, Longdo Map

Integrate Api e.g. dlt, scg, cpf, Integrate gamebrand e.g.

sexy, pg, sbobet, sms, email, line api

Database Postgresql, Mysql, Sql Server, Mongodb, Redis, SQLite

Config Replication Master and Slave Server Postgis, Geo, Stored Procedure, Database trigger

Server Ubuntu, Window Server, Nginx, Kubernetes, Docker, Kong

Api Gateway, GCP, AWS

Tools Gitlab, Bitbucket, Github, Jira, Asana, Gather Town, Slack,

CircleCI, GitlabCI, Netlify, Cloudflare, Prometheus, Grafana,

gRPC, RabbitMQ

Research Microfrontend, Service Mesh Isito, ArgoCD, Jenkins, Apache

Kafka, Terraform, Ansible, SonarQube

Elasticsearch, Opensearch, LevelDB, Firebase

Flutter, Laravel, Spring Boot, .Net Core, FastAPI, Rust, Golang, Solidity, Wab3, Ethers.js, Kotlin, SwiftUI, Unity,

Facebook API, WebRTC, WASM